WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
I never thought he'd attempt to use
the Fourth Hokage's Jutsu.
But it's still just this level...
It's completely different
from the original one.
That Tsunade...
Incredibly strong as always.
I remember a long time ago,
getting punched by her and
knocked back nearly 100 meters...
At any rate, Naruto's hopeless.
Are you okay?
Jiraiya, was it you...
who taught him that Rasengan?
Rasengan...?!
I'm his teacher, after all.
Humph... You and the Fourth Hokage are
the only ones who can use that Jutsu.
Are you in your right mind...
showing someone Jutsu
that he can't master?
Don't give him false hope.
That's why the oblivious kid starts joking
about becoming a Hokage!
It's no joke! Stupid! Stupid!
If I have three days,
I'll master this Jutsu!
You said it, kid.
Men don't go back on their word!
Hah! I stand by my words.
That's my Ninja Way.
Then... how about a wager?
A wager...?
I'll give you one week.
If you can master that Jutsu,
I'll acknowledge that you have
what it takes to become the Hokage
and give you this necklace.
Tsunade-sama! That's the precious...!
I don't need such a sorry necklace!
Don't say such things, Naruto...
That's the only one of its kind in this
world.
And you could buy three mountains
if you were to sell it.
It belonged to the First Hokage.
A-Awesome...
Well, that'll be fine!
He'll do anything for money...?
Good...
However, you lose if you can't master
the Jutsu in one week!
And you'll give me all the money
you have on you.
Oh! Gama-Chan!
When did she...?!
Tsunade-sama! Why?
That necklace is...
He won't be able to do it, anyway...
Let's go, Shizune.
She never once used
that necklace for a bet...
You don't have to answer right now.
However, I want it in a week.
The First Hokage's
Inheritance
The Necklace That
Calls Upon Death
Huh? Who is it this late at night?
Okay, okay. I'm coming.
I'm sorry to bother you so late, Naruto-kun.
I need to talk to you...
As for me, I'm going to get
a good night's rest and train tomorrow!
I'm sorry. But I didn't want you
to misunderstand Tsunade-sama...
As well as the necklace...
Humph! I couldn't care less
about an old lady like that!
Tsunade-sama is not the type
of person you think she is!
Don't speak of her like that
when you don't even know her!
I-I'm sorry... for raising my voice.
She didn't used to be like that.
She was a kind person
who loved the village.
But, she changed...
After that day...
That day?
What's that day?
The day she lost her dreams,
her love, her hopes... everything.
All that was left was
that necklace of memories...
It's as precious as life to Tsunade-sama.
It's really not something
to be offered in a bet.
I don't care about that!
She bet it on her own, right?!
Besides... that necklace is really
not something for you to wear.
It's not just a necklace!
It doesn't acknowledge anyone
other than Tsunade-sama.
If someone else wears it,
that person inevitably...
...dies!
Nawaki, happy twelfth birthday!
I'm not a kid anymore,
so I don't need gifts on my birthday!
What're you saying?
You're still a kid, aren't you?!
But never mind that.
Hurry up and open your present!
You'll definitely be pleased!
Nee-chan, could this be...?
Yes... It's the First Hokage's,
our grandfather's necklace!
I love you, nee-chan!
I thought it'd be better than me having it.
You've been wanting it all along, right?
Take good care of it.
Not just this necklace!
This village is grandfather's treasure!
I'm going to protect it!
Nawaki...
I'm the grandson of the Hokage who
built the Village Hidden in Leaves, so...!
You said it.
Men don't go back on their word!
Right!
Someday, I'll become just like Grandfather.
And the Hokage name will be mine!
Becoming the Hokage is my dream!
Take off your headband, Nawaki.
Just hurry up and take it off.
I have another present for you.
It's a charm to make
your dream come true.
It's best if you don't look
at the remains.
There's nothing wrong with that,
is there?
Even if she were to look,
she wouldn't be able to determine
that it's her little brother.
Enough, Orochimaru!
We are at war, now.
All Shinobi end up like this.
There are no doctors on
the battlefield, so...
However, children really get
much too excited, don't they?
Especially on the day after
they receive a present.
Not just this necklace...
This village is grandfather's treasure!
I'm going to protect it!
First, in a mission where
a Four-Man Cell must act alone
for a long period of time
in enemy territory,
by deploying one of the four
to be a medical specialist,
the survival rate as well as
the mission success rate
should go up significantly.
Therefore, establishing a framework
to foster Ninja possessing
advanced medical skills
and the development of
a medical institution
should be considered
an urgent task for the present!
Yes indeed, it's as you say.
But we're in the middle of a war now.
It takes too much time to
establish a medical framework.
And at present,
we don't have enough knowledge...
Enemies don't wait.
What did you say?! Hey, old man!
Then we'll never...
I agree with her.
I don't want the lives of the Shinobi
who died to be for naught.
There should be something
we can learn from that.
Excuse me!
Thanks for earlier.
What you said was right.
Umm...
It's late.
Shall I walk you home?
What? Is that okay with you?
Where's your home?
The other way.
Then don't bother.
I don't mind.
I also want to talk with you.
And I would always use this path
to the Academy to pick up my little sister.
I loved this path.
What? You loved?
Yeah. In the battle when the Leaf
was attacked at night one year ago,
my little sister was...
This man... is the same as me.
Tomorrow's mission will be
within enemy lines...
Fighting and losing cherished people
is not the only way for a Shinobi.
Uh-huh.
I'm living in a world of Shinobi
where death always hovers.
I want to risk my life to bring
this war-torn world under control.
I love this village and my comrades.
So I want to protect them.
Since my little sister died,
that sole thought has sustained me.
So I'll become the Hokage...
An existence that protects everyone...
Becoming the Hokage is my dream.
Dan...
I'd like you... to take this.
Hang on, Dan!
Tsunade... I don't want... to die yet.
I have many things that I must... do.
Don't talk, Dan!
His kidney has been blown out...
It's futile even for Tsunade
who is known as one of the Sannin...
I... must not... die here.
It'll be okay. I stopped the bleeding.
So it'll be okay... You'll be saved, Dan!
Really?
Thank goodness...
Dan! Hang on!
Dan!
Damn it! Don't come out...
Stop... Please stop!
Stop... Stop...
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop!
That's enough. He's dead!
You understand, don't you, Naruto-kun...?
Ever since that day,
Tsunade-sama has been...
in a constant turmoil.
Naruto-kun...?
I'm heading out... for training!
Oh, you are already at it, I see!
Hi, welcome!
Why are you here?
You're cold. Don't say that.
Jiraiya-sama...
Shizune, could you leave us?
It's been a while.
I want to drink with her again.
Master, alcohol! And some radish!
Coming up!
I'm counting on you, Jiraiya-sama.
Your radish is ready.
Ooh. This looks good.
At any rate, to think you'd still be taking
good care of that necklace...
I thought you'd have lost it
long since to gambling.
It's a memento of those two, right?
Is he on your mind...?
Who?
Naruto.
Not particularly...
Still, it's immature,
taking on that kid as an opponent...
He shouldn't be able to master
that Jutsu in a week, right?
That's not what's called a bet.
What's with the fit of despair?
It's not a fit of despair!
Are you going to meet
Orochimaru again?
I can tell by looking at Shizune's face.
I don't know what kind of deal
he proposed,
but don't rush to a decision.
And... let me just tell you one thing.
The successive line of Hokage
have protected
the Leaf Village and those living in it.
They brought troubled times under control
and helped the village to prosper.
They risked their lives
for this dream, this ideal!
You're not someone who can't understand
the feelings of the previous Hokage.
Just try doing something
to betray the Leaf Village.
When that happens, I'll kill you myself!
It has nothing to do with me now!
A person who has experienced
the death of people close to them
and doesn't feel anything
is just a butcher.
You're different, aren't you?
No one cared for the welfare
of the villagers more than you.
At that time, too...
That's enough with the lecture!
Why... did you bring that kid?
Becoming the Hokage is my dream.
He resembles him, doesn't he?
His age is about the same, too...
Not just that...
Becoming the Hokage is my dream!
Jeez, you do nothing,
but reckless things.
Do you want to die?
You're still a Genin,
so on the battlefield just run away.
Don't tell a man to "run away"!
That dream... And his cockiness as well...
No good! Damn it! Damn it!
Tomorrow, for sure...!
My head hurts.
I totally got sick from drinking,
thanks to her...
It seems Naruto never came home
last night...
He's such a fool.
Why don't we make a deal?
I'll resurrect the little brother
and man, both of whom you loved...
with the Forbidden Jutsu I've developed.
Don't you want to see those two,
Tsunade?
If I treat your arms...
What do you intend to do with them?
This time, I will completely
destroy Leaf Village!
No! You must not believe
in their sweet talk...
Their wishes...
Moreover, Tsunade-sama, your wishes...
And dreams... Did you forget them?!
I'll be straight with you.
Tsunade, the village has demanded
that you become the Fifth Hokage.
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
Damn it! What am I doing?!
I fell asleep at such
an important time!
Moreover, today is the day
of the bet!
Meanwhile, I don't even know where
Granny Tsunade has gone to!
My training is not completed yet...
I've got to play it by ear
and rely on a one-shot deal!
Next time:
"Yes or No! Tsunade's Answer."